[{"question": "Odometer is to mileage as compass is to", "options": ["speed", "hiking", "needle", "direction"], "answer": "d"}, {"question": "Marathon is to race as hibernation is to", "options": ["winter", "bear", "dream", "sleep"], "answer": "d"}, {"question": "Window is to pane as book is to", "options": ["novel", "glass", "cover", "page"], "answer": "d"}, {"question": "Cup is to coffee as bowl is to", "options": ["dish", "soup", "spoon", "food"], "answer": "b"}, {"question": "Yard is to inch as quart is to", "options": ["gallon", "ounce", "milk", "liquid"], "answer": "b"}, {"question": "Elated is to despondent as enlightened is to", "options": ["aware", "ignorant", "miserable", "tolerant"], "answer": "b"}, {"question": "Optimist is to cheerful as pessimist is to", "options": ["gloomy", "mean", "petty", "helpful"], "answer": "a"}, {"question": "Reptile is to lizard as flower is to", "options": ["petal", "stem", "daisy", "alligator"], "answer": "c"}, {"question": "Play is to actor as concert is to", "options": ["symphony", "musician", "piano", "percussion"], "answer": "b"}, {"question": "Sponge is to porous as rubber is to", "options": ["massive", "solid", "elastic", "inflexible"], "answer": "c"}, {"question": "Careful is to cautious as boastful is to", "options": ["arrogant", "humble", "joyful", "suspicious"], "answer": "a"}, {"question": "Pen is to poet as needle is to", "options": ["thread", "button", "sewing", "tailor"], "answer": "d"}, {"question": "Secretly is to openly as silently is to", "options": ["scarcely", "impolitely", "noisily", "quietly"], "answer": "c"}, {"question": "Embarrassed is to humiliated as frightened is to", "options": ["terrified", "agitated", "courageous", "reckless"], "answer": "a"}, {"question": "Pride is to lion as shoal is to", "options": ["teacher", "student", "self-respect", "fish"], "answer": "d"}, {"question": "Artist is to painting as senator is to", "options": ["attorney", "law", "politician", "constituents"], "answer": "b"}, {"question": "Exercise is to gym as eating is to", "options": ["food", "dieting", "fitness", "restaurant"], "answer": "d"}, {"question": "Candid is to indirect as honest is to", "options": ["frank", "wicked", "truthful", "untruthful"], "answer": "d"}, {"question": "Guide is to direct as reduce is to", "options": ["decrease", "maintain", "increase", "preserve"], "answer": "a"}, {"question": "Oar is to rowboat as foot is to", "options": ["running", "sneaker", "skateboard", "jumping"], "answer": "c"}]
